<form>    
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsDnsProvider</id>
        <label>DNS Provider</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select the DNS provider for the DNS-01 Challenge and Dynamic DNS. This is optional, since certificates will be requested from Let's Encrypt via HTTP Challenge when this option is unset. You mostly need this for Wildcard Certificates, and for Dynamic DNS. To use the DNS-01 Challenge, enable the checkbox in the advanced mode of a Reverse Proxy Domain. To use Dynamic DNS, enable the checkbox in a Reverse Proxy Domain or Subdomain.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsDnsApiKey</id>
        <label>DNS API Key</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[This is the standard field for the API Key. Enter the API key for the selected DNS provider. Leave this empty if no DNS provider is set.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsDnsSecretApiKey</id>
        <label>DNS Secret API Key</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[A few DNS providers like porkbun also need a Secret API Key set. Leave this empty if other or no DNS providers are set.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsSimpleHttp</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Http</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Optionally, enter a URL to test the current IP address of the firewall via HTTP protocol. Generally, this is not needed. Caddy uses default providers to test the current IP addresses. If you'd rather use your own, enter the https:// link to an IP address testing website.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsInterface</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Interface</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Optionally, select an interface to extract the current IP address of the firewall. Attention, all IP addresses will be read from this interface. Only choose this option if you know the implications.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsCheckInterval</id>
        <label>DynDns Check Interval</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Interval to poll for changes of the IP address. The default is 5 minutes. Can be a number between 1 to 1440 minutes.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsIpVersions</id>
        <label>DynDns IP Version</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Leave on None to set IPv4 A-Records and IPv6 AAAA-Records. Select "IPv4 only" for setting A-Records. Select "IPv6 only" for setting AAAA-Records.]]></help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.DynDnsTTL</id>
        <label>DynDns TTL</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Set the TTL (time to live) for DNS Records. The default is 1 hour. Can be a number between 1 to 24 hours.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
</form>
