<form>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.enabled</id>
        <label>Enabled</label>
        <type>checkbox</type>
        <help>Enable or disable Caddy Web Server.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsEmail</id>
        <label>ACME Email</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <hint>info@example.com</hint>
        <help>Enter the email address for certificate notifications.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsAutoHttps</id>
        <label>Auto HTTPS</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the auto HTTPS option. On (default) creates automatic certificates using Let's Encrypt without needing any configuration.</help>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsDnsProvider</id>
        <label>DNS Provider</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help>Select the DNS provider for the DNS-01 Challenge. This is optional, since certificates will be requested from Let's Encrypt via HTTP Challenge when this option is unset. You mostly need this for Wildcard Certificates. If you have your own Wildcard certificate, you can import it to System Trust Certificates and use it in the advanced mode of a new Reverse Proxy Domain. To use the DNS-01 Challenge, enable the checkbox in the advanced mode of a Reverse Proxy Domain.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.TlsDnsApiKey</id>
        <label>DNS API Key</label>
        <type>text</type>
        <help>Enter the API key for the selected DNS provider. Leave this empty, if no DNS provider is set.</help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
    <field>
        <id>caddy.general.accesslist</id>
        <label>Trusted Proxies</label>
        <type>dropdown</type>
        <help><![CDATA[Select an Access List of Trusted Proxies. If Caddy is not the first server being connected to by your clients (for example when a CDN is in front of Caddy), you may configure trusted_proxies with a list of IP ranges (CIDRs) from which incoming requests are trusted to have sent good values for these headers. Additionally, set the same Access List to the Domains your Trusted Proxy connects to.]]></help>
        <advanced>true</advanced>
    </field>
</form>
